Where'd it go?
I'm sorry for the trouble, Ishikawa.
Nothing to be sorry for.
You're sure it dropped over here?
Yes. Maybe if I'm careful, I can help you look.
Or maybe not. Stay there where it's safe, buddy.
Broke the glasses you just bought,
only to drop your contact lens, too.
You should add more blueberries to your diet.
True. You know you're free to stop your search whenever, right?
I won't be offended.
He's kneeling?
But why is he kneeling?
Yonaki, what'd you do to make Ishikawa bow down?
More importantly, it's past time to leave,
so I'll tell them to go home,
then nonchalantly ask what's going on.
Let's go!
Wow, you actually found it.
Now keep an eye on that thing.
And was someone else here, or am I going crazy?
Well, I thought I saw someone, but I couldn't really tell.
Guess they had somewhere to be.
Dude, that's kinda creepy.
Did you, uh, make sure everything's locked up tight?
I'm sorry, Dad.
I couldn't make the first move against Yonaki.
Sengoku?
We'll be right back.
Possibly.
Oh.
Bye, Akane.
See you tomorrow.
Goodbye.
Act fast.
Don't let your precious chance pass you by.
You okay?
No, not really.
Why?
Because you called the Onagi by his first name!
I'm sorry.
Talking like you're as close as can be.
Let me stop you right there!
Just because I call him by his first name doesn't mean anything, so don't read into it!
But I want to be allowed to call him by his first name too!
That's what's wrong?
What are the odds of him getting upset if I told him I'd like to call him Akane?
I would get slim to none.
You honestly think so?
Like without a doubt?
My little weirdo.
Don't start with that if you aren't gonna finish.
Hey guys!
Have you seen Yanagin?
You just missed him.
Aww.
Remy has a whole bag of yummy cookies for him.
Kion Kion will eat them.
No thank you, I'm super full.
That's a double shame.
Sakura bakes the best cookies.
Wait, Kono made those?
What's it to you?
Like everything?
But you're full.
You got Remy local, didn't you?
Totally.
The one day the bus is super, super light, I'm in a super, super hurry to get home.
The universe must super hate us.
Something up, Biomorta?
The bus is running super, super, super, super, super late for some reason.
That's a lot of supers.
I'm pretty sure Akane takes the bus to school.
And it's really windy today.
Where's the bus?
So cold.
You out here by yourself, handsome?
Were you talking to me?
Ayasaki?
Nope.
Remy isn't here right now.
What are you doing?
Trying to hit.
Trying what?
The longer I look at you, the cuter you seem to get.
If you got time, why not waste it on me?
Should I?
I don't think I know this game.
Stop dishing your cheese when he clearly isn't eating it.
You aren't wanted here, so take a hike.
A Hori?
No.
I'm just somebody passing through.
We've never met before, okay?
So the Hori's not up for grabs?
This world ain't fair, I tell ya.
I'm outta here.
Less talkie, more wealthy shades.
While you...
Oh, I'm sorry.
I thought you were finished.
No, I was...
It's your turn, isn't it?
Mmm.
We forgot the next line, so we're skipping it, hot stuff.
By all means.
Oh yeah, that's it.
Hear the news?
Bus is gonna be 15 minutes late.
Wait, are you being serious?
Always am, babe.
And man, is it Nippy?
I'm not sure that you're passing through.
We've never met before, okay?
So the Hori's not up for grabs?
This world ain't fair, I tell ya.
I'm outta here.
Less talkie, more wealthy shades.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I thought you were finished.
No, I was...
It's your turn, isn't it?
Mmm...
We forgot the next line, so we're skipping it, hot stuff.
By all means.
Oh yeah, that's it.
Hear the news?
Come on, babe.
And man, is it Nippy.
They came to let me know.
I can wait 15 minutes.
I won't freeze by then.
Thanks, random person.
I got him!
Good things to those who wait.
Emphasis on wait.
You want a cup of cocoa, Yanagin?
What?
Here.
No variety?
I figured we wouldn't fight if they were all the same.
Hey, where's Remy's drink?
Uh...
Yanagin, look!
We also brought some cookies!
That's...
Uh...
Kind of...
They're guaranteed to be good.
Kono baked them.
How sweet.
But, um...
Why do this?
Waiting in the cold all alone is just the worst.
No, you don't have to.
We aren't bothering you, right?
Like, just say the word and we can go.
No!
Please don't leave!
Yeah.
Hm?
You've got mail?
From my dad.
He was excited about getting home from work early today.
He wants to go somewhere special for dinner to celebrate.
Yanagin, guess what?
Hm?
This is Amiyomura's plan.
He told us to stall you while he got us some nice warm drinks.
I'm curious where you got the shades for this masterful plan I cooked up.
From the student council room.
So whose are they?
I'm sorry.
I just ate five cookies in a row without thinking.
I really should've worn my coat.
Me too.
The knife in the skirt sounds way colder.
Hmm, wear one and see for yourself.
Pass.
Hori, may I please have a cookie?
Of course.
Much obliged.
I've been informed certain students have been skipping elective classes.
Because they're frequently used as study halls.
An utter and tragic waste.
This vital time in your education should be spent wisely.
Therefore, I won't permit tardiness from Class 3-6.
All students are to be on time next week.
Are we clear?
Yes.
Sengoku's texts are weird.
Sometimes I find myself wondering, did he really send this?
Yeah, I get that.
What are you saying?
Us a perfectly normal text?
Maybe at first.
They do start off normal enough.
Gotta maintain some sense of shame when you text.
Don't reveal those to the public.
You aren't the only one.
Me and Moira's texts occasionally sound like a girl-type dumb.
That's news to me.
Pack me up here, Yana.
Holy crap.
Uh, dude, was that the sound of your head colliding with the desk?
What makes you think that?
Why on earth would I hit my head on the desk?
Those are some delirious.
Yonagi, are you tired?
A rough night's sleep?
Hanks' thoughts?
Well, actually, since you asked,
You can't be late for a week?
A campaign to end all tardiness.
Makes it sound like a heroic journey.
I don't see how.
I have trouble waking up, and stressing about this rule makes it hard to sleep.
If I'm tardy even once, they'll display my name and photo for the entire school.
Whoa, that's harsh.
Yonagi is tardy quite a bit.
Go to bed early.
Well, I tried that, but woke up at odd hours, so I still felt tired.
Yeah, it's a vicious cycle.
We just have two more days left, though. I'll tough it out.
Cool. As long as your alarm's set, you'll be golden.
That's right. Even set a backup alarm in case the first one didn't cut it.
Oh, I guess I should say I was setting a backup.
It stopped yesterday, and I barely made it in time.
Dead battery?
I wish. I found it broken on the floor next to my bed.
Like beyond repair.
Okay.
I don't think I remember moving it at all, but it was just lying there when I got home from
school.
My bed was a mess as well, but my parents said they hadn't gone near my room.
I don't know what's going on, but it's strange and, well, scary.
Oh, but I digress. None of you care about that.
Yes, we do. Go on.
That does sound scary.
I know you aren't hurt, but shouldn't you be more concerned?
Carry some salt with you everywhere you go.
Wait, why salt?
So when you can't wake up, is it due to sleep paralysis or what?
I just oversleep out of habit.
And your sleepy self is down an alarm clock.
Will one be enough to do the job?
What if I gave you a wake-up call?
Huh? Yeah, good idea.
You should still set your alarm clock to be on the safe side, but I'll ring your cell tomorrow morning
and make sure that you get out of bed.
Uh...
And you send them a text.
Do it for the lulz.
I'd rather call like Miyamura if you're just gonna tease me about the text.
But Yanagi needs your text, Prez.
Calls work too.
The thought of you all calling that early when I don't do mornings.
You have full permission to hang up without talking.
Waking you up is what matters.
I apologize in advance.
What should a wake-up text say?
Alright.
I can't let them down.
What?
It's morning.
No way.
It's only 1.30.
That's night.
I'm going back to sleep.
Hey, Akane.
This is your wake-up call.
No, it's not.
What?
So tired.
Hey, you answered.
Good morning.
Better get up, Rose.
I'm going back to sleep.
Hey, Akane.
This is your wake-up call.
No, it's not.
What?
So tired.
Hey, Akane.
This is your wake-up call.
No, it's not.
What?
I'm tired.
Hey, you answered.
Good morning.
Better get up, Rose.
18-year-old Akane Yanagi is profoundly bad at getting out of bed.
Oh, the text.
Hey, I woke up in time.
I really owe you one.
I'm happy for you, but the way you hung up without a word definitely stopped.
I am so sorry.
I don't even remember since I was half asleep.
Oh, there you are.
Thank you for the text.
I laughed until my sides hurt.
You laughed?
Then I was up and at him.
A good hearty laugh did the trick.
So round two's a go for tomorrow?
No, but thank you.
I should learn to be more independent, I think.
Plus, I heard my alarm go off before anything.
All right.
But if you change your mind, just give me a shot.
I will.
Little did Yanagi know how much he'd regret this decision then.
For his remaining alarm clock would also fall silent.
You both yourself.
Can't choose between oolong and green tea?
Hey!
Yanagi.
No, it's fine. I simply needed a drink. As long as it quenches my thirst, it'll do.
And this one happens to be brand new, I believe.
I've noticed you're relaxed with your classmates and Yoshikawa, yet act so courteous with the rest of us.
I suppose it's something of a habit. I'm a bit more casual when I speak with people I'm close to.
The same goes for people I want to be closer to.
I worded that horribly, so please don't misinterpret what I said.
And it's not that I don't want to be friends with you or anyone else I'm more well-mannered around.
The damage is done.
That's some aura. Wonder why Mr. Doom and Gloom is so down in the dumps.
What's the matter?
Well, I'm all ears, pal. Give me them details.
Go on and get it off of that chest. And shake till you feel better.
Up yours.
Senkoku!
Okay, that's on Shu for being a pest.
I'm a lovable goofball!
Did you and your girl have an argument?
Rejection.
Shu, he says Ayasaki's single now.
No, I did not! We're still dating!
So Yanagi rejected you.
In here, I thought you were tight.
He said he's polite with me because he has zero intentions of getting any closer.
That's why he's polite.
You want half of this chocolate Danish thing?
Sure. How kind.
I can't finish it on my own.
So it's a Danish?
A really sweet Danish.
All that chocolate gave me heartburn.
You like it?
Uh-huh.
It's yummy.
Oh, cool deal.
Just, um, pace yourself, okay?
Roger.
Stop smirking like you beat me at something!
And you stop acting like you're the only one that he's overly formal with.
What you said. It's no biggie.
I know, but still...
The Prez, Ayasaki.
Everyone and their grandmother likes Yanagi.
Okay, I won't let it bother me.
I'll treat him the same way that I always have.
Ah, stuck in the friend zone.
You know what it means to be out of the friend zone, right?
Sengoku!
Sorry!
Please forgive me!
I assure you it's okay, as long as it quenches my thirst.
I don't think it did.
You know, if it tastes too strong, I wouldn't mind drinking it in your stead, so...
I'll snag you another drink real quick-like.
It'll def-taste better.
Thank you, but only if you really want to.
Totes!
Here you...
I mean, trade ya.
Cool deal?
Uh, yeah, that's great.
Lots of kids in my class don't like this juice.
I've heard its flavor can be best described as...
Sucky.
Uh, is he trying to be more casual with me?
Hey, listen.
Talk to me however you prefer.
Don't force yourself to use slang and stuff.
But, I am...
Right!
Yes!
Ten-four!
All right!
Glad you understand.
Sengoku's creeping me out.
Oh?
How come?
Because of that big dopey grin?
Holy cow!
That is really creepy.
The creep slapped me!
Sengoku's a pretty straightforward guy.
He probably made up with Yanagi.
Yay!
Yanagi's here!
Where's he heading to, though?
I'm returning to the classroom.
Remy won't let you take another step until you talk more casually.
Aw, don't laugh me off.
If only Sengoku were as blunt as Ayasaki when he spoke.
Yay!
Yanagi's here!
Where's he headed to, though?
You're stuck near than a box of tissues.
We're friends, aren't we?
Talk casually!
No.
That would just be an imposter.
You look like you're gonna cry.
What's wrong, huh?
I could do not.
Right.
You ready for this, Iyuda?
Yeah, yeah!
Don't hold back!
Because I sure won't.
Here I go.
Ah-ha!
What the heck is this game?
He said he could catch a blade with his hands.
Since I thought it was a bold claim, I asked for a demonstration.
Which he then failed.
Man, I so would have caught it if it had been a katana.
He would make a murderer out of our sweet Yanagi.
Tell us you how nuts he is.
I wonder.
Suppose I took a page out of Iyuda's book and said I could catch a blade with my hands.
Would Yanagi have asked me to demonstrate my skills, too?
Um, hard to say.
The people he's drawn to.
They tend to possess rather cheerful demeanors, don't they?
You mean airheads like Yoshikawa?
If air-
Cheerful people are easier for him to get along with, I don't stand a chance.
Just embrace your inner airheadedness.
When I saw Yoshikawa the other day...
...and he's not even listening to me.
Oh, where's she going?
Oh, I'm so sorry!
She mistook the wall for a person and apologized?
Well, I've done that.
Oh, but wait, there's more.
Yes, she glared daggers at the wall she bumped into.
I will never be anything like Yoshikawa.
Neither.
Okay, but how?
Shu might be the type of person to imitate if you want to act friendlier, dude.
Imitating, Yura?
I compromised far too much, so no!
Better him than the girl who glares at walls.
I'll show you how it's done, okay?
Hang tight and watch.
Watching?
Yanagi!
That's me.
Tickle torture!
Akane's ticklish on the soles of his feet, too!
Your turn.
No way!
Nope, not a chance!
Never!
Idiot!
That kind of talk won't get you anywhere!
You're better friends than you used to be!
Now get over there and tickle that man!
All right, I have to practice before the real thing, though.
You're seriously practicing for a tickle fight right now?
There.
I feel violated from how sensual that was!
Yo, that took me by complete surprise!
Keep it rated, Jade!
I don't know what I did, or why you're angry with me.
What you did is called a grope.
Thank goodness I practiced.
Yanagi would have hated that.
So you're groping people now.
Why do you pop in at the worst possible times?
Doing a bit of role play, are we?
And Sengoku's playing the handsy pervert.
Hey, now!
What part are you playing, then?
Yanagi.
Throw in the setting while you're at it!
I'm gonna trade or something!
If the scene's Akane getting felt upon a train, who should I be?
Since it's a role you know inside and out, just be an airhead.
You really called somebody an airhead just now!
Is the class president bullying me?
No, calm down.
He's just frustrated.
Wants to bridge a gap between a friend, but his missing parts.
What gap?
We're all peas in a pod.
But he's unsatisfied?
Am I the only one who thinks we're friends?
This isn't about you and your life's not in danger!
So cut it out!
Aw, come on.
Don't fight, guys.
Really, people?
Timing!
The press is being mean to me.
You're bullying?
Say it ain't so!
You don't hate the hush!
I really can't see Sengoku as a bully.
You take his side like it's the one with the cream.
Guess I never noticed.
Sengoku and Yanagi sure are good friends.
Discretion, please!
Guess what?
Sengoku told me he wants to be like Shu.
He did?
But why?
I like him just the way he is.
What a surprise!
To walk in Shu's shoes,
I suggest you start with a new do and go for more!
I didn't mean your looks!
First you're a pervert,
and now you're Iyuda.
Talk about a busy day.
Uh, yeah.
Huh?
The pervert?
No, he's confused!
Meet me in the school capital room later!
Wait, what?
What'd I do?
Infuriated me!
Wait, what's that?
You know, Miyamura and Sengoku
should have a great friendship.
Why's that?
You know, be honest
So you know,
what's the culture difference?
Is that you're having to buy?
It looks like it's not used
for more than a phone.
Do you have to buy Überlieft
over the years?
Wasa
I'm gonna be back again
Don't forget that
I don't want to stop the day that I'm too bright
I don't want to stop the day
Ah
What are you doing?
That's the day
Ah
I'm gonna be right
You need
Ah
また想いが
張り裂けそうなのに
URLより短い
言葉にしかできない私です
Ah
I'm so sad
でも君に跳べるように
出会えるように
if you did it